

Pragya Singhal

Content writer

I like to put a lot of my emotions, experiences, and opinions into what I write. I like being able to make my writing something other people can connect to, or relate to in some way by generalizing the thoughts and experiences I'm writing about. I believe I have a strong relationship with the words which makes it easier to write creative content.

📍 Indore, India

in linkedin.com/in/Pragya Singhal

9826470655

singhalpragya.wordpress.com/

EDUCATION

schooling

The Emerald Heights International School

03/2016 - 03/2020 Indore

– college

Prestige Institute of management and research

05/2020 - Present Indore

Courses

Bcom(hons)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Content writing intern

Mmf infotech

12/2021 - 04/2022 Indore, India

Content writing intern

Kidadl

06/2022 - 08/2022 Uk

Content creator

TechInfini Solution Pvt. Ltd.

09/2022 - 04/2023 Indore, India

SKILLS

Copywriting

Communication

Creative writing

PERSONAL PROJECTS

blogs

• Wrote 2 blogs on my wordpress page.

CERTIFICATES

Inter-state football tournament u-14 (09/2015)

All India hockey IPSC tournament u-19 (10/2019)

Niit nguru (03/2016 - 03/2017)

IT wizard plus program

Helen O' Grady (05/2016 - 04/2017)

Drama certification

INTERESTS

travelling

talking to new people

singing

Playing football